http://boldlygo.org/legal

Disclaimer, Terms of Use & Privacy Policy — BoldlyGo Institute
AcademyDonateContact
BoldlyGo Institute Disclaimer, Privacy Policy and Terms of UseThis website is maintained and operated by BoldyGo Institute, Inc., a New York nonprofit corporation (“BoldlyGo Institute”, or “BGI” or “we” or “us).By logging into this website (the “Site”) and using any features or applications available through the site, you (and if you are a corporation, partnership, company, association or other entity, your members, directors, officers and employees)(collectively “You”): (1) agree to be bound by these Terms of Use (“TOU”); (2) agree to our Privacy Policy, which is set forth below; and (3) agree to be bound by other legal notices that may be posted on this Site from time to time. The legally binding terms of these documents set out your rights, obligations and restrictions regarding your use of the Site.DisclaimerNeither BoldlyGo Institute nor this website are affiliated with, associated with, authorized by, or endorsed by CBS Studios and its interests in the STAR TREK television series and all related series.Privacy PolicyBoldlyGo Institute (BGI) has created this privacy notice to explain how we use information that you may provide while visiting the Site and to demonstrate our firm commitment to Internet privacy. BGI may modify this policy from time to time, so we encourage you to check this page when revisiting this Site.How We Use Your InformationWhen you register, contribute, sign up to volunteer, or take any other action on this Site, we may ask you to give us contact information, including your name, address, employer/institution, telephone number and/or e-mail address. We may obtain information about you from outside sources and add it to or combine it with the information we collect through this Site. We use this information to operate this Site and BGI, including usage to comply with IRS nonprofit organization reporting guidelines; to send news and information to you about BGI; to solicit your contributions and input to and/or participation in programs, events and activities; and to obtain and confirm RSVP’s to events, meeting, workshops and programs. We use your e-mail address to send such information by e-mail and may use your telephone number to call you for these purposes.We will never provide your e-mail address or any of your personal information to any other person or organization, for any purpose except to expedite the organization and implementation of BGI’s programs and events with our partners or members acting on behalf of BGI. Submitting your personal information including e-mail address on this page will sign you up to receive e-mails only from BGI AND DonationPay.org (see below) AND from organizations clearly identified on this Site as allied organizations which have partnered with or are working with BGI in organizing and/or implementing BGI’s programs.Credit Card Information; Protection of Personal InformationWhen you donate online to BoldlyGo Institute, we collect credit card information from you. That information is used solely by our contribution processing service, DonationPay.org, for processing your donation; is not maintained by BGI; and is never disclosed to anyone, for any other purpose other than for processing your contribution, under any circumstances. After making a donation through DonationPay, your name, donation amount and contact information are forwarded to BGI so that we may (1) issue you a donation receipt in addition to the acknowledgment you receive from DonationPay, and (2) maintain a database of donors, whom we shall occasionally contact regarding BGI programs.DonationPay.org uses industry standard security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under their control. Their privacy policy and terms of use may be found here: https://www.donationpay.org/site/privacy-policy.Permission to access your credit card information is granted only to you and to DonationPay.org employees or contractors who need to know that information to provide services to you. Although we make good faith efforts to store information collected by this Site in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee complete security.ChildrenBGI does not solicit personally identifiable information from children. Visitors who are under 13 years of age should ask their parent(s) or legal guardian for assistance when using the Site and should not submit any personally identifiable information to the Site. For example, visitors under 13 years of age should not make donations or take any actions on or through this Site.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Some parts of this Site may be password-protected. We may use a cookie (cookies reside on your computer and are under the control of your browser) to enable you to return to password-protected areas of the Site without having to re-enter your password. If you wish to disable these cookies, the help portion of the tool bar on most browsers will tell you how do that. If you set your browser to disable cookies, however, you may not be able to access certain parts of this Site.AdvertisingWe may place online advertising with third-party vendors, including Google, which will be shown on other sites on the internet. In some cases, those third-party vendors may decide which ads to show you based on your prior visits to the site. At no time will you be personally identified to those third-party vendors, nor will any of the information you share with us be shared with those third-party vendors. If you prefer to opt out of the use of these third-party cookies on the site, you can do so by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.Data TrackingIn order to better serve our supporters, we use cookies and periodically analyze web logs. We may also use third-party services such as Google Analytics. This helps us understand traffic patterns and know if there are problems with the Site. We may also use embedded images in emails to track open rates for our mailings, so that we can tell which mailings appeal most to BGI supporters.URLs contained in emails may contain an ID that enables us to correctly identify the person who takes an action using a web page. We may occasionally present a shortened URL that references a longer URL which contains an id—we do this to simplify the display, to prevent links from becoming broken when copied, and to ensure compatibility with email programs which do not handle long URLs. When a shortened URL is displayed in an email, you will see the full URL in the browser's address bar when you access the page.Links to Other SitesThe privacy policies and practices contained in this Privacy Statement do not apply to ANY external links. This Privacy Statement only applies to this Site or any future sites that we may develop. It does not cover sites to which are linked by this site or sites for which we are not responsible ("linked-sites"). These linked-sites will have their own policies and practices which may be different from ours. We therefore encourage you to familiarize yourself with the policies and practices of the linked-sites, especially if you provide personal information to them.Amendments and Consent to This Privacy StatementWe retain the right to amend or otherwise update this Privacy Statement at any time. By using this Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information as we have described. If we change our policies and practices, we will post the changes in our Privacy Statement so that you are always aware of them. With this knowledge, you can make an informed decision about whether you wish to provide personal information to us.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, you may contact us by sending an e-mail via our Contact page.Terms of UseBy using this Site in any way, you agree that you will not copy any information from the Site without our written permission, attempt to sell such information or offer it for sale in any form, in any way, or use any of the information on the Site for any commercial purpose including but not limited to advertising or promoting any product, service, or organization.Limit of Liability and ReleaseThe information set out on this Site is correct to the best of BGI’s present knowledge, information and belief.You understand and agree, however, that BGI does NOT represent or warrant that any information set out in the Site is in fact accurate or current. Under no circumstances will BGI be responsible for any loss or damage, resulting from anyone's use of the Site whether online or offline. The Site is provided "AS-IS" and (to the extent legally permitted) BGI expressly disclaims any warranty of fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement, and further expressly disclaims any implied warranty. BGI cannot guarantee and does not promise any specific results from use of the Site.By using this Site in any way, you agree to release and forever discharge BGI and its members, directors, officers, employees, consultants and agents from any and all claims and demands whatsoever in nature and/or action, causes of action (whether known or unknown), damages, costs, attorneys' fees or costs of litigation, which you may have or may have arising from, based on or resulting from your use of the Site or any information contained in, set forth or linked to by or on the Site.Intellectual PropertyYou agree that all copyright and other rights in and to the computer programs, computer applications, web applications, database programs, web content files and all written, graphic, audio and audiovisual works incorporated into and utilized on the Site shall be and remain the sole and exclusive property of BoldlyGo Institute (“BGI Intellectual Property”). You may not copy, modify, publish, transmit, distribute, perform, display, or sell any such BGI Intellectual Property.Maintenance and OutagesBGI reserves the right to interrupt the Site with or without prior notice for any reason or no reason. You agree that BGI will not be liable for any interruption of the Site, delay or failure to perform. You further understand that BGI has the right at any time for any reason or no reason to change and/or eliminate any aspect(s) of the Site as it sees fit in its sole discretion.You agree that BGI is not responsible for any error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, communications line failure or any problems or technical malfunction of any telephone network or lines, computer systems, servers or providers, computer equipment, software, failure of email on account of technical problems or traffic congestion on the Internet or at any Site or combination thereof, including injury or damage to users or to any other person's computer related to or resulting from participating or downloading materials in connection with the Site.Except where restricted or prohibited, in no event will BGI be liable to you or any third person for any indirect, consequential, exemplary, incidental, special or punitive damages, including lost profits arising from your use of the Site, even if BGI has been advised of the possibility of such damages.. Some jurisdictions do not allow the disclaimer of warranties or exclusion of damages, so such disclaimers and exclusions may not apply to you.
Copyright 2020 BoldlyGo Institute, Inc. All rights reserved.Disclaimer, Privacy Policy & Terms of UseDISCLAIMER: Neither BoldlyGo Institute nor this website are affiliated with, associated with, authorized by, or endorsed by CBS Studios and its interests in the STAR TREK television series and all related series.For a listing of the state nonprofits disclosures, click here.
HomeWho We AreSpaceBitesContact
